<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ChattyAI</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy Policy for chatGenix AI Chat Bot This Privacy Policy outlines how OpenChat AI Chat Bot the Chat Bot we us our collects, uses, and protects the data and information of users you your when you interact with the Chat Bot, which generates chat, images, and transcriptions using OpenAI APIs. Information Collection The Chat Bot may collect the following types of information: Chat Data: The Chat Bot may collect and store the chat data, including messages, images, and transcriptions, that you input or generate during your interactions with the Chat Bot. Usage Information: The Chat Bot may automatically collect certain usage information such as IP address device information browser type operating system referring URLs usage patterns and other similar data when you use the Chat Bot. Cookies: The Chat Bot may use cookies or similar tracking technologies to collect and store information about your interactions with the Chat Bot such as your preferences session information and other usage data. Use of Information The Chat Bot may use the collected information for the following purposes: Providing Services: The Chat Bot uses the collected information to generate chat, images, and transcriptions based on your interactions and requests. Improving Services: The Chat Bot may use the collected information to analyze usage patterns diagnose technical issues and improve the performance and functionality of the Chat Bot. Personalization: The Chat Bot may use the collected information to personalize your experience with the Chat Bot, such as remembering your preferences and displaying relevant content. Communication: The Chat Bot may use the collected information to communicate with you respond to your inquiries or requests and provide updates or notifications related to the Chat Bot. Information Sharing The Chat Bot may share the collected information with third parties in the following cases Service Providers: The Chat Bot may share the collected information with third-party service providers who assist us in providing and improving the Chat Bot such as hosting data analysis and customer support. Legal Requirements: The Chat Bot may share the collected information in response to legal requests court orders or other legal processes or to protect our rights property or safety or the rights property or safety of others. Data Retention The Chat Bot retains the collected information for as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected, unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law. Security The Chat Bot takes reasonable measures to protect the collected information from unauthorized access disclosure alteration or destruction. However please note that no method of transmission over the Internet or method of electronic storage is 100% secure, and we cannot guarantee absolute security. Third-Party Links The Chat Bot may contain links to third-party websites or services. Please note that this Privacy Policy does not apply to such third-party websites or services, and we are not responsible for their privacy practices. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of those third-party websites or services before providing any information to them. Children\'s Privacy The Chat Bot is not intended for use by children under the age of 18. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children. If you are a parent or guardian and believe that your child has provided us with personal information, please contact us immediately. If we become aware that we have collected personal information from children without verification of parental consent, we will take steps to remove that information from our servers. Updates to Privacy Policy The Chat Bot may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the updated Privacy Policy on the</string>
</resources>